Dang... I finally climbed up the ladder
enough to get a TV appearance.
These greenrooms sure do
make you restless, though.
Reigen-san, you're up.
All right. Let's do this.
"Supernatural Detective! Do Spiritual
Powers Actually Exist? Special" "MG Tea"
(Get ready, wake your psyche up, MOB!)
(Get ready, dig your anger up, MOB!)
(Get ready!)
Coming down,
could you fill your satisfaction?
You're a MOB.
Can't you feel your own frustration?
Coming down,
could you fill your satisfaction?
You're a MOB.
What do you want to be?
Wear your overflowing emotions
on your sleeve and break it down
What do you see once you go
beyond your limits?
(99.9! 99.9)
The mysterious percentage
Cr yin' my life, or yin' my psyche,
Cr yin' my heart in such commonplaces!
Is that your ideal? Is that your mind?
It all begins when it hits 100
The MOB is alive. The MOB is high.
The MOB is staying frustrated, aren't you?
Is that your ideal?
Is that your mind? Right now
YOUR LIFE IS YOUR OWN.
(Get ready, wake your psyche up, MOB!)
"Mob Psycho 100 II"
(Get ready, dig your anger up, MOB!)
(Get ready, wake your psyche up, MOB!)
(Get ready!)
"A boy was possessed by a fox after
playing Kokkuri-san after school!?"
"A boy was possessed by a fox after playing
Kokkuri-san after school!?" Oh, this must be it.
Oh, this must be it.
Jodo-sama's return to TV.
R-Reigen?!
What the heck is he doing?
And now... Will we be able to save the poor,
"Host" "Ebihara Morizo" And now...
Will we be able to save the poor,
"Host"
"Ebihara Morizo"
"Host" "Ebihara Morizo" unfortunate
young man that's been possessed?
Unfortunate young man that's been possessed?
Let's introduce our two powerful helpers!
The first one needs no introduction.
The president of the Rising Sun
Spiritual Union, Jodo Kirin-sensei!
"Jodo Kirin"
"Jodo Kirin" He's solved devastating
problems for many. He's the best of the best!
He's solved devastating problems for many.
He's the best of the best!
The other is making his
first appearance on TV.
Reigen Arataka-sensei!
Why, hello there. I'm Reigen Arataka.
You can find my business in Seasoning City.
What are some of your accomplishments
up till now, Reigen-sensei?
It's hard to choose just one...
Oh, but I did defeat the Dragger.
"Mogi Tatsuya”
Huh? That's awesome.
Looks like we can expect great things.
And now, let's bring out the boy.
To be extra careful,
since he may freak out,
We have him securely bound.
"Go to Reigen-sensei"
What do you think?
I see...
The footage we just watched
mentioned that he was possessed by a fox
after playing the Kokkuri-san game.
But to be more precise,
it's a ghost of a Rüppell's fox,
which are usually found in North Africa.
What's this? He was able to precisely
deduce the kind of ghost it is!
What do you think, Jodo-sensei?
The poor child...
being strapped down like that.
I'm hoping we don't have to keep
those things on him much longer.
I see. So we all feel the same.
And now, we're finally going to
witness the public exorcism!
But before that,
a word from our sponsors.
When we're back on air, we're going
to have Jodo-sensei do the exorcism.
Actually, why don't we have
Reigen-kun give it a shot?
--Wha--
--No one wants to see an old man.
Let's show the country how
a next-generation psychic does things.
Wasn't I just supposed to sit
there and comment today?
I'm trying to give you the spotlight here.
But if you're not up to the task, very well.
I'll do it, just as it says in the script.
The script?
I see!
One moment! I'll do it after all.
Okay... sure.
Reigen-sensei's going to
perform the exorcism this time.
We're coming back from commercial!
"Supernatural Detective
Specia!!!"
"Supernatural Detective Special!!!” And it looks
like we're just about ready for this public exorcism.
And it looks like we're just about
ready for this public exorcism.
The one performing this exorcism
is an exciting newcomer
who has had a meteoric rise!
Reigen Arataka-sensei! Are you ready?
Leave it to me! I, Reigen Arataka,
shall accept this job!
I shall successfully get rid of this spirit!
Live or not, this is still a TV show.
It's all a setup written by some scriptwriter.
If I do some random exorcism,
that'll quietly be the cue
for the boy to calm down
and the studio audience to clap.
Then the host will praise me,
and the show will be over.
"Splashity Splash"
Salt Splash!
And he just started throwing
a ton of salt outta nowhere!
The spirit possessing the boy
seems to be struggling in agony.
It's working! It's really working!
But it has never worked before!
This kid is acting!
Now that I know that,
I'm not pulling any punches!
Sorcery Crush Special!
Air Banishing Salt...
Punch!
A clean hit!
Well, it's been about 30 minutes
since the exorcism started,
but apparently, the spirit
just refuses to leave.
--Talk about resilient.
--Evil Spirit Detox Acupressure!
Holy Water Chop!
For real!
I've already used up all my special moves
"Salt Splash" "Graphic Exorcism" "Aroma Runway
Express” I've already used up all my special moves
I've already used up all my special moves
"Sorcery Crush" "Hypnosis Punch" "Anti-Possession Jumping
Knee Strike"" I've already used up all my special moves
"Sorcery Crush" "Hypnosis Punch"”
"Anti-Possession Jumping Knee Strike"
"Sorcery Crush" "Hypnosis Punch" " Anti-Possession Jumping Knee
Strike" and now I'm trying to keep things going with ad-libs!
And now I'm trying to keep
things going with ad-libs!
"Cheeseburger Tornado" "Banishing Salt Punch" and
now I'm trying to keep things going with ad-libs!
"Cheeseburger Tornado"
"Banishing Salt Punch"
All right, let's have our
other psychic step in.
--Huh?
--Jodo Kirin-sensei, if you would.
W-Wait... Was I just an opening act?
Is he going to take all the glory?!
Hang on a sec. I've almost got it.
Switching right now would be--
Look, we're live.
Reigen-kun, good work the last 30 minutes.
You wily, scheming old man!
All right, Jodo-sensei! Let's see you work!
My spotlight!
What am I supposed to exorcise here?
This boy isn't even possessed.
He's just acting.
Huh? "Say what?--1?"
Huh?
Oh, come on, you geezer!
Get a clue!
Why'd you ruin all that setup
the program built up for you?!
You are absolutely correct!
I'm impressed you were able to see the truth
when everyone in the studio has
been tricked this whole time!
A true psychic has just been revealed!
My name is Fukuda Suzuo, and I'm a child
actor from the Mongolian Spot Agency!
That was some brilliant acting!
Thank you very much!
I could barely tell he was acting!
Sci-fi researcher, Mogi-san,
what did you think?
I'd like to ask that gentleman over there
what all that "exorcism" crap was about.
What were you doing to a spirit
that didn't even exist?
Reigen-sensei, I'm sure our viewers
are wondering that as well.
Could it be... that you actually
don't have spiritual powers?
Come, now. Let's just say
this is how he works.
Excellent work, Jodo-sensei!
It should've been completely obvious
if the boy was possessed or not...
If you're a true psychic, that is.
Oh, I beg your pardon.
It's not like I'm referring to Reigen-san.
I'm sure he was trying to liven things up
for the sake of the program.
But I can guarantee that we
didn't ask him to do that.
What? Really? Poor Fukuda-kun.
It was basically torture.
Then what in the world were
you doing for 30 minutes?
Some new kind of dance?
I mean... It appeared as though that
boy was possessed by some spirit...
So I exorcised it.
Even if he was merely acting
like he was possessed,
spirits could come by at any moment.
What? A spirit was here?
I didn't even notice.
When did it appear?
About 30 minutes ago...
Right on the dot! I never knew
evil spirits were so punctual!
What kind of spirit was it? Huh?
What kind of spirit was it?
It was a man...
I-I think he was German...
Stop it, me! If you say another word...
It was Beethoven.
> Du-du-du-dunno! )
Did you watch yesterday's ep
of Supernatural Detective?
"That one thing"” "Reigen Arataka" "A psychic who's an expert on fraud"
"Salt" "On-air incident” "Psychic fraud"” I did! I laughed so hard!
"[Fraud] Reigen Arataka is crazy" "Anonymous Table Salt:" "Anonymous Table Salt: If that were
me, I'd end myself” "Anonymous Table Salt: Salt Splash" That was basically a public execution.
"[Fraud] Reigen Arataka is crazy" "Anonymous Table Salt:" "Anonymous Table
Salt: If that were me, I'd end myself” "Anonymous Table Salt: Salt Splash"
"[Fraud] Reigen Arataka is crazy" "Anonymous Table Salt:" "Anonymous Table Salt: If that
were me, I'd end myself” "Anonymous Table Salt: Salt Splash" That Reigen guy is hilarious!
That Reigen guy is hilarious!
"S-lol-A-lol-L-lol-T S-lol-P-lol-L-lol-A-lol-S-lol-H" "Con Man" "Crazy Salt Splash" "Exorcism dance” "Herf lol"
"lolololololololololololololol™ "What is this?" "Crazy Salt Splash” "Hilarious That Reigen guy is hilarious!
"S-lol-A-lol-L-lol-T S-lol-P-lol-L-lol-A-lol-S-lol-H" "Con Man" "Crazy Salt Splash" "Exorcism
dance™” "Herf lol" "lolololololololololololololol™ "What is this?" "Crazy Salt Splash” "Hilarious"
Looks like Reigen's dug
himself into a hole...
"Naritasan" Looks like
Reigen's dug himself into a hole...
"Naritasan"
There's no way that guy's a fraud.
I wonder if Reigen-san has
a plan to get out of this.
They're apparently making
a group for his victims.
Wanna go?
But we're not victims, though.
So he was a con artist after all.
It's probably his fault
we aren't getting any job offers.
I knew there was something off about him.
I'm gonna feed the media
even more bullcrap about him!
"The Next Day"
Hey, I might just be remembering wrong,
but isn't the place you work called
Spirits and Such Consultation Office?
It is.
Th-Then is your master's name...
Reigen Arataka?
Huh? Yeah, it is.
Y-You haven't heard?
Your master's getting bashed like crazy
on TV and the Internet!
We're getting a lot more actual jobs now.
If I become famous, I might be able to
break through to other media platforms.
"Spirits and Such Consultation Office" "The star psychic of the 21st century who defeated the Dragger" "Welcome
to Reigen Arataka's homepage!! If I become famous, I might be able to break through to other media platforms.
If I become famous, I might be able to
break through to other media platforms.
That's all part of his plan.
"We're closed today"
"Unknown"
"Unknown" Did he really
think people wouldn't find out?
Did he really think people
wouldn't find out?
And he calls himself a spirit medium?
I've actually been a victim
of spiritual fraud myself.
"The 'Self-Proclaimed' Psychic. Isn't He a Fraud?"
They wanted me to undress for an exorcism.
God damn it! I was set up!
Those conniving bastards!
They used me as a scapegoat to boost
their ratings for like 30 seconds?!
That conniving old man!
For now, I need to contain this and ensure
I don't become an even bigger meme.
"Anonymous Table Salt: Reigen's the real deal. He's actually performed an exorcism on me, and my shoulders and back feel so
much lighter now. I felt better immediately.” For now, I need to contain this and ensure |I don't become an even bigger meme.
"Anonymous Table Salt: Reigen's the real deal. He's actually performed an exorcism on
me, and my shoulders and back feel so much lighter now. I felt better immediately.”
"Anonymous Table Salt:
I bet that's Reigen, isn't it?"
Gah! They figured me out!
"Name:" "Wha--? Of course I'm
not. I'm trying to be objective here..."
"Sent"
"Anonymous Table Salt:
Okay, Ruppell's fox"
"Get lost, you fraud"
"Do you even realize you're a criminal?"
"Reigen's watching~"
"I found Reigen's
high school graduation photo lolol"
Is that how it's gonna be,
you little bastards?
Like I'd let a bunch of little shits who
don't know a thing about hard work beat me!
But the title and reputation of
"scam artist psychic"
spread like wildfire across media platforms
like a game of telephone.
And in three days, being the ultimate evil
had basically become Reigen's public image.
You can't be serious!
This isn't true at all!
How dare they spread these lies about me?
"Self-Proclaimed New Star of the Psychic World Reigen: The Scam Artist Psychic
His Unbelievably Bold Tricks!!!" How dare they spread these lies about me?
"Self-Proclaimed New Star of the Psychic World Reigen:
The Scam Artist Psychic His Unbelievably Bold Tricks!!!"
"Happy Trails"
So basically,
I need you guys all to be my witnesses to
stop these guys from calling me a fraud.
All you have to do is talk to the media.
Huh?
Hey, why aren't you being
as annoying as usual?
Leave, now.
You can't fool us anymore.
Huh?
Hey, you can't be serious!
You probably thought we were prime prey!
We're not falling for that!
And here I thought he was a little cute, too!
Well, I guess the only thing I can do now
is wait until this all blows over.
What the heck? Are they actually
staking out my place?
There he is! That's Reigen Arataka!
Shit!
--Don't run away!
--Wait!
What was that so-called exorcism
you performed on that show?
Don't you think you need
to explain yourself?
You could at least give us some answers!
Are you off today?
The people aren't going to
be satisfied with this!
Everyone has their eye on you!
--Yeah!
--You can't run from this!
--A press conference!
--How about holding a press conference?
Huh?
A press conference?
Reigen Arataka, the man
who's garnered attention
for allegedly conning people
with psychic scams,
announced that he will be holding
a press conference tomorrow.
"Reigen Arataka (28)" "Alleged Psychic Scammer” "Plans to Hold a Press
Conference” We believe the subjects that will be discussed will include
"Reigen Arataka (28)" "Alleged Psychic
Scammer" "Plans to Hold a Press Conference"
"Reigen Arataka (28)" "Alleged Psychic Scammer” "Plans to Hold a
Press Conference” if his previous activities were indeed illegal,
if his previous activities
were indeed illegal,
--and if he actually even
possesses spiritual powers.
--That's...
--and if he actually even possesses spiritual powers.
"To Arataka -- From Mom"
“I'll show you a top secret way to..."
"You seem to be in a lot of trouble. I prepared an apology for you to say at the press conference,
so if you get in trouble, just read that. Learn your lesson from this, quit this scamming business,
and get a real job. I know your dad doesn"t say it much, but he's worried about you. You should come home. You haven't
been home lately at all. This is the perfect opportunity for us to all have a family meeting. I'm on your side.”
"Apology"
"Thank you all for gathering here today. I'm sorry that you all had
to take the time to show up today over my own personal actions."
"(1 day ago)"
Man... It'll be morning soon.
"Mob Psycho 100 II"
--He's here!
--Reigen has appeared!
Damn, that's bright.
Shit.
I thought I'd have a chance if
we were just going to argue,
but now my head's completely blank.
Calm down.
First, you need to get the reporters
to have a good impression of you.
F-First, I'd like to thank
you all for gathering...
Why did you all gather here today, anyway?
It's pretty common to suddenly get tired
of all this shit at the last minute.
What's with that attitude?!
--What?!
--Are you mocking us?!
You're the one who said you'd
hold a press conference!
That's because you guys kept
stalking me to my house.
You basically made me hold this thing.
I have a few questions regarding
the fraudulent acts you've committed.
Hang on a sec.
By "fraudulent acts,"
are you referring to my business?
Is there anyone here that can actually prove
I don't have any spiritual powers?
Or maybe any victims who can
prove they've been scammed?
There are a lot of people who've
reported that they've been scammed--
Right. Self-proclaimed "victims."
Why are you saying it like that?!
Because it hasn't been proven.
Unless and until they are,
I can still call myself a psychic.
I'm not a criminal.
I'd be careful with how you
phrase things if I were you.
All right, I have a question.
Go ahead.
Do you actually have spiritual powers?
No comment.
Why won't you answer?
Because you won't be satisfied
unless I say "no."
I can't prove that I have spiritual powers
since you all lack them yourselves.
Are you really going to try
to talk your way out of this?
Judging from the broadcast the other day,
you do seem like you're
excellent at ad-libbing.
Tch.
Oh? Did you just click your tongue?
No, I was just testing the mics.
"Cola" "Potato Chips" No,
I was just testing the mics.
"Cola"
"Potato Chips"
"Cola" "Potato Chips" Uh-oh,
now he's copping an attitude.
"Cola"
"Potato Chips"
This guy's finished.
"Press Conference" "TekeTekeFanClub@gakkokaidan -7 minutes
ago" "Mic test #Press Conference" This guy's finished.
"Press Conference" "TekeTekeFanClub@gakkokaidan
-7 minutes ago" "Mic test #Press Conference"
"Press Conference" "TekeTekeFanClub@gakkokaidan -7 minutes ago" "Mic test
#Press Conference" When did you start this psychic business of yours?
“"Press Conference” "Level of sorry: O What's the criminal getting all pissy
for? Lololol #PressConference" When did you start this psychic business of yours?
"Press Conference" “"IDrinkPufferfish@usotsuki_usouso —20 seconds ago" "Mic test
lolololol #Press Conference" When did you start this psychic business of yours?
When did you start this
psychic business of yours?
About four years ago.
What were you doing prior to that?
I worked at some company.
Did that company have anything
to do with psychics?
No, not at all.
He's actually answering the questions.
What kind of problems did
people come to you with?
Stiff shoulders, spirit photos, and stuff.
Did they see any results?
Those cases have been solved.
Any particular case that stands out?
Getting rid of some urban legends.
Have you ever had
any conflicts with your clients?
I have not.
Have you ever sold any expensive
salt or prayer beads?
I have not.
Apparently, information about when you were
a student is spreading over the Internet.
That doesn't matter.
According to your graduation
essay, you wrote this...
"I want to be somebody."
What made you get into the psychic business?
Why?
Reigen-san looks pretty pale...
D-Don't keep making the
media outlets your enemy.
How wonderful. He's at a loss for words.
Something's wrong.
He doesn't have his usual zing.
Great Master Reigen...
What's wrong?
Why did I decide to live as a psychic?
It's not like it's lucrative,
and it's usually troublesome.
Thinking back,
"Super delicious! The next generation” "Water Dispenser” "The
ultimate natural spring water to keep you healthy” Thinking back,
"Super delicious! The next generation” "Water Dispenser”
"The ultimate natural spring water to keep you healthy”
"Super delicious! The next generation” "Water Dispenser” "The ultimate natural spring
water to keep you healthy” there was a time when I always did everything efficiently
there was a time when
I always did everything efficiently
and was filled with curiosity
about everything.
But then I got bored, quit my job,
and rented that office on a whim.
I ended up getting into this facade of
a job because of an ad I saw in a magazine.
"Power Stone" "You can become a millionaire, too!!" |I ended up
getting into this facade of a job because of an ad I saw in a magazine.
I ended up getting into this facade of
a job because of an ad I saw in a magazine.
That's right... I actually
meant to quit a long time ago.
"Spirits and Such Consultation Office"
"3 Years Ago"
"3 Years Ago" Thank you very much!
"Spirits and Such Consultation Office"
"3 Years Ago"
My body felt so heavy,
but now I'm fine!
Man, I'm bored.
As it stands, I'm no
different from a masseur.
Guess it's about time to wrap things up.
I wonder what I should do next.
Being a Pl sounds pretty fun,
but maybe not, since apparently they mostly
do investigations on cheating spouses.
Excuse me.
I came here because I saw your sign.
Sure thing.
How may I help you?
Er... Oh, it's just a kid.
What do you want, boy?
Um, I'm an esper.
Wha--?
There are times when I can't
control my powers very well,
and it's scary.
You shitty little brat.
This must be a prank.
Did someone tell you to
come here and tell me that?
No. I haven't been able to
talk to anyone about this.
I thought you might be the same as me...
If I tried, I could see spirits, too.
A pathological liar?
No, maybe it's an over active imagination.
Either way, he seems rather troubled by this.
Well, come on in.
Okay.
I was troubled a lot when I was a kid, too.
What's with this kid?
He's staring at me with
eyes brimming with hope.
This is serious.
This kid's in his own fantasy world.
I'll just come up with something
to get him to go home.
Listen. Just because you have psychic powers
doesn't make you any less human.
It's the same as people who are fast,
people who are book smart,
and people with strong body odor.
Psychic powers are just
another characteristic.
You must embrace that as a part of
yourself and continue to live positively.
The truth behind one's charm is kindness.
Become a good person. That is all.
May I come to talk to you again?
Yeah, I don't know about that.
I'm pretty busy, you know?
Anyway, you should go home for tod-- Hot!
Hey, don't get bur--
Hey... You said you could
see ghosts, too, right?
Do you know how to exorcise them, too?
All right. Come again tomorrow
around the same time.
What? Really?
I'll show you how to use your powers.
Back then, I couldn't help but admire
this kid that walked into my life.
I wanted to grasp something for myself, too.
I wanted to become someone special.
Yet this is the result.
I haven't changed at all since then.
I just kept using him.
In the end, I couldn't become anything.
Maybe I was the one who was holding
him back from his youth the most.
Man, I said something really awful back then.
He wanted to change,
and yet I tried to cage him in.
Hey, Mob... Are you watching?
"#ReigenArataka
58,699 tweets"
You've grown up so much. You know that?
That doesn't answer anything!
--What kind of answer is that?!
--What was that silence?
--Who was that message to?
--We don't understand!
Answer us!
It's an earthquake!
We are experiencing an extremely
powerful earthquake!
"Psychics exist. Says the psychic
#Press" "So cool #Press Conference"
"Anacatesthesia FTW #Press Conference"
"I feel the power #Press Conference"
"CG technology is getting incredible lately #Press"
Where's this press conference being held?
O-Our cameras!
"Spirit"
I-Is Reigen doing this?!
Telekinesis?!
Such incredible power!
"Naritasan"
That doesn't seem like Reigen-san.
This is getting serious...
Nii-san! Nii-san!
How can you remain so calm?!
Are you the one doing this?!
P-Please do something!
Is this due to your spiritual powers?
Gee, I wonder what's going on.
Please, stop this!
What the hell's going on?!
Are you done asking me if I'm a fraud or not?
In that case, I'll be ending
this press conference.
H-Hey!
What's going to happen to us?!
Beats me.
You should probably concentrate
on finding your next big story.
One of the lights fell!
"One moment please"
"Cola"
What the hell was that? Such bullshit.
"Cornered
- True Identity~"
Why... are you here?
Everyone is dreaming
Just because.
Everyone is dreaming Let's get the hell out of
here. They're gonna be running around for a while.
Let's get the hell out of here.
They're gonna be running around for a while.
Of a world filled with bright futures Let's get the hell
out of here. They're gonna be running around for a while.
Of a world filled with bright futures
I'm sure that it's painted in vivid colors
Hey... Do you know?
That have nothing to do with me
Know what?
What I really am...
"Why am I crying?"
"Why am I crying?” Haven't you seen
any of the stuff on the web or magazines?
"Why am I crying?"
"Why am I crying?”
I've always known... from the beginning.
"Should I be hated by someone?”
What my master really is...
"When did this all happen?”
The answers are nowhere to be found
...is a genuinely good guy.
My emotions began to stir and
whispered faintly in a blue tone
I still remember all the words
that came flooding out
I don't know when it happened,
but my heart has started opening up
I don't know when it happened, but my heart
has started opening up Man, I'm starving.
I don't know when it happened,
but my heart has started opening up
I don't know when it happened, but my heart has
started opening up Let's have some ramen and head home.
I don't know when it happened,
but my heart has started opening up
I don't know when it happened, but
my heart has started opening up Okay.
I don't know when it happened,
but my heart has started opening up
Oh, by the way, Master, happy birthday.
Mob's finally telling Tsubomi-chan
how he really feels about her?
And he's going to try to place
within the top ten in a marathon?
Welp, looks like he's going to need my help.
Next time on Mob Psycho 100 Il Episode 8:
"Even Then
- Continue Forward~."
"Even Then - Continue Forward~" First-press limited
edition? That is the absolute best decision.
"Even Then
- Continue Forward~"